This Time It Gets Even More Brutal.
I Spit on Your Grave III: Vengeance Is Mine is a horror,
thriller film directed by Richard Schenkman.
Jennifer Hills is still tormented by the brutal
sexual assault she endured years ago.
She’s changed identities and cities, reluctantly joining a support
group where she begins to piece together a new life.
But when her new friend’s murderer goes free and the tales of serial rapists haunt her, Jennifer will hunt down the men
responsible and do what the system won’t – make them pay for their crimes in the most horrific ways imaginable.
Only this time, no jury may be able to save her.
Jennifer Hills / Angela Jitrenka, played by Sarah Butler.
Marla, played by Jennifer Landon.
Johnny, played by Jeff Branson.
Therapist, played by Harley Jane Kozak.
Lynne, played by Karen Strassman.
Mallory, played by Alissa Juvan.
I Spit on Your Grave III: Vengeance Is Mine is a 2015 American rape and
revenge film, directed by Richard Schenkman (credited as R.D.
Braunstein) from a screenplay by Daniel Gilboy.
It is the third film of the remake trilogy and the
fourth overall installment in the series.
The film stars Sarah Butler, Jennifer Landon, Doug McKeon and Harley Jane Kozak.
Butler reprises her role as Jennifer Hills from the 2010 film I
Spit on Your Grave (a remake of the 1978 original).
The film explores themes of rape, police,
detective, group therapy, investigation.
The tone is dark and intense.